broward.edu 2014-06-18

# Broward College - Internet Privacy Statement

as required by Broward College policy 6Hx2-8.02

Thank you for visiting the Broward College website. Your privacy is very important to us. Simply stated, our policy is to collect no personal information about you when you visit our website unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us.   

In addition, we gather information regarding the volume and timing of access to our website by collecting information on the date, time and pages accessed by visitors to the website. We do this so we can improve the content of our website, and this information is not shared with other organizations. Again, only aggregate information is collected, and individual visitors' personal information is not identified.

If you choose to share personal information with us -- by sending us a message or filling out an electronic form with personal information -- we will use the information only for the purposes you authorized. Some of the information may be saved for a designated period of time to comply with the state of Florida's archiving policies, but we will not disclose the information to third parties or other government agencies, unless required or authorized to do so by state or federal law.   

The Broward College website has links to sites outside our domain. BC is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those other sites.

If you have other questions about our privacy policies, or have ideas about improving our policies, please feel free to e-mail us at [webmaster@broward.edu](mailto:webmaster@broward.edu).
